{
  "results": [
    {
      "question": "What is the correct translation for 'telephone'?",
      "correct_answer": "el telefono",
      "incorrect_answers": ["el agua", "un paraguas", "una bicicleta"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say 'Good Morning",
      "correct_answer": "Buenos dias",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Buenos noches", "Buenas tardes", "Adios"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say 'Good afternoon'?",
      "correct_answer": "Buenas tardes",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Buenos dias", "Adios", "Buenas noches"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say 'Good evening'?",
      "correct_answer": "Buenas noches",
      "incorrect_answers": ["unas llaves", "Muchas gracias", "Adios"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct translation for 'Please'?",
      "correct_answer": "Por favor",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Perdon", "Hola", "izquierda"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say 'Thank You'?",
      "correct_answer": "Gracias",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Adios", "derecha", "Perdon"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct translation for 'Thank you very much'?",
      "correct_answer": "Muchas gracias",
      "incorrect_answers": ["No se", "!Perdon!", "!Salud"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say 'Sorry'?",
      "correct_answer": "Perdon",
      "incorrect_answers": ["No se", "Gracias", "Por favor"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say 'Hello'?",
      "correct_answer": "Hola",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Por favor", "Gracias", "No se"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you say 'Good-bye'?",
      "correct_answer": "Adios",
      "incorrect_answers": ["izquierda", "Donde esta la playa", "Buenas noches"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct translation for 'right'?",
      "correct_answer": "derecha",
      "incorrect_answers": ["izquierda", "Donde esta la playa", "Buenas noches"]
    }
  ]
}
